akonter.com 2018-12-15

# Privacy Policy | Akonter

Privacy Policy for [http://www.akonter.com](http://www.akonter.com/ "http://www.akonter.com/")

At [Akonter.com](http://www.akonter.com/ "http://www.akonter.com/"), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by [http://www.akonter.com](http://www.akonter.com/ "http://www.akonter.com/") and how it is used.

We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used.

Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.

This Privacy Policy also explains how we process 'personal data' about people in the European Union (EU), as required under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

## Registering Your Account

In order to become a Akonter member, you must first register for an account on the Site. To register for an account, you are required to provide a chosen username and password and your email address which we use only to track your account or communicate with you. We do not make your email address and password publicly available and we strongly discourage you from doing so. registering using a service Facebook or Google allows the adfty to make a request for data about you such as picture and your email address. We do not marketing or sell or share your email address with anyone else.

Once a member, you may provide additional publicly accessible information in various areas of the Site, including the “Profile” area, comment areas, bookmark submissions, etc. This includes describing yourself, your opinions and your personal contact information. Providing this type of personal information is entirely optional, and because we are unable to control how others may use such personal information, you do so at your own risk.

In order to share story information with people you personally know who are not Akonter members, you may enter their email addresses into our tell a friend. This information will be used by us to send a link directing them to this Site, including a message that you write. The email addresses of people that you invite will be used only to send your invitation.

## Profile

All profiles on Akonter are public. If any real user has an active profile with a few exclusive articles in addition to the interaction with other articles by "likes or comments" on them, his/her profile will be fully public. To delete your profile, go to the profile settings and click the "delete" button. Remember, all your data and articles will be deleted, keep in mind you can not undo the deletion.

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, [http://www.akonter.com](http://www.akonter.com/ "http://www.akonter.com/") makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

[http://www.akonter.com](http://www.akonter.com/ "http://www.akonter.com/") does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Akonter.com uses diverse services from the American Google Inc and Twitter Inc and AddThis.. These services include Google Analytics, Google Adsense, Google reCaptcha, Google Fonts, Google and Twitter plugins, Addthis Share Buttons.

## DoubleClick DART Cookie

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.akonter.com. .:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.akonter.com and other sites on the Internet. .:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....

Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.akonter.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

[http://www.akonter.com](http://www.akonter.com/ "http://www.akonter.com/") has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.akonter.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

Google Analytics

We use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of this site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve this site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use](http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html) (as amended for government websites) and the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html). You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by [disabling cookies](http://www.usa.gov/optout_instructions.shtml) on your browser or you may opt out of tracking by Google Analytics by visiting <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-GB>.

Google reCaptcha: 

We use the reCAPTCHA service provided by Google Inc. (Google) to protect your submissions via internet submission forms on this site. This plugin checks if you are a person in order to prevent certain website functions from being (ab)used by spam bots (particularly comments). This plugin query includes the sending of the IP address and possibly other data required by Google for the Google reCAPTCHA service. For this purpose your input will be communicated to and used by Google. However, your IP address is previously truncated by Google within member states of the European Union or in other states which are party to the agreement on the European Economic Area and is, as such, anonymized. Only in exceptional cases is a full IP address transmitted to a Google server in the United States and truncated there. On behalf of the operator of this website, Google will use this information to evaluate your use of this service. The IP address provided by reCaptcha from your browser shall not be merged with any other data from Google. 

This data collection is subject to the data protection regulations of Google (Google Inc.). For more information about Google's privacy policy, please visit: <https://policies.google.com/privacy>

By using the reCAPTCHA service, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. 

Twitter: 

Our website uses social plugins (“plugins”) from twitter.com, which is operated by Twitter, Inc. (“Facebook”). These plugins are branded with a Facebook logo or with a phrase such as "Twitter Social Plugin". When you visit a website on our website containing a Twitter Social Plugin, your browser creates a direct connection to the Twitter servers. The content of the plugin is transmitted directly to your browser by Twitter and is then incorporated into the website. Twitter, in turn, is aware of every time the website is accessed. If you have a Facebook profile, the company is able to associate the website visit to your profile by using JavaScript and setting cookies. If you interact with plugins on a website, for example by clicking the “Like” button or replying to a message, this information will be sent directly to Twitter and stored there. With the right browser plug-in you can prevent this information from being transferred, but please keep in mind that Facebook Social Plugins will no longer work properly. 

For more information on the purpose and scope of data collection and further processing and use of data by Twitter, as well as your rights and changes to settings you can make, please review the [Twitter privacy policy here](https://twitter.com/privacy). 

Google:

Our website uses social plugins (“plugins”) from Google.com, which is operated by Google, Inc. (“Google”). These plugins are branded with a Google logo or with a phrase such as "Google Social Plugin". When you visit a website on our website containing a Google Social Plugin, your browser creates a direct connection to the Google servers. The content of the plugin is transmitted directly to your browser by Google and is then incorporated into the website. Google, in turn, is aware of every time the website is accessed. If you have a Google profile, the company is able to associate the website visit to your profile by using JavaScript and setting cookies. If you interact with plugins on a website, for example by clicking the “Like” button or replying to a message, this information will be sent directly to Google and stored there. With the right browser plug-in you can prevent this information from being transferred, but please keep in mind that Google Social Plugins will no longer work properly.

For more information on the purpose and scope of data collection and further processing and use of data by Google, as well as your rights and changes to settings you can make, please review the [Google privacy policy here](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

AddThis

We use social sharing buttons from AddThis, kinds of visitor data does AddThis receive

AddThis provides with tools that collect information from visitors. This information does not directly identify an individual and is instead designed to identify the devices used by your visitors. However, in certain circumstances, the visitor may opt to share their email address with AddThis to facilitate the services. These email addresses are not used for online behavioral advertising. you can prevent this information from being transferred using the AddThis [opt out](https://www.addthis.com/privacy/opt-out). This opt out will prevent advertisers from receiving any data about the opted-out visitors. 

more information on AddThis’ practices. Please review our full [Privacy Policy](https://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy) and [Terms of Service](https://www.addthis.com/privacy/terms-of-service) for more details. 

## Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

Privacy Policy Online Approved Site

## Notification of Changes

This Privacy Statement may change from time to time and any changes will be published on the Site. The revised version will be effective as of the date and time it is published. Please check back periodically to be informed of any changes.

## Update

This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Saturday, May 25th, 2018.

Should we update, amend or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here.

## Contact

If you require any more information have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [Contact Us](http://www.akonter.com/static/contact-us/).

Akonter.com

ATTN: Akonter Privacy Issues
